yes you did it you turned the 100 into
the M everything was going perfect now
I'm at the point where I'm very
confident in my strategy like the hate
doesn't get to me anymore I feel like I
already went through the hardest part
now we're going to try and take these
130,000 into
$260,000 officially the trade that we
caught last night has given us 100K
floating and profit right now you guys
can see everything right here to
Perfection they up
$39,000 this looks literally insane in
the p&l
chart and
then stop loss hit on the first one
second one almost hit it h we already
hit stop loss on one buy we're about to
hit stop loss on these other two trades
right
now wow we're officially under six
figures
this is NFP the news have completely
gotten me it is the first Friday of the
month and I had absolutely no
idea wow wow wow wow we have officially
blown the account and at the
end oh the account is officially blown
literally 3 months out the windows the
trade that we predicted it
perfectly so I'm going to leave social
media for as long as I feel like because
you know this whole challenge stuff I've
been doing this now
for 3 months and it's been very
stressful um I've gave it my off and
clearly in the last 2 3 weeks I've just
been completely breaking my training
plan everything has just pretty much
gone down the drain and I'm going to
enter a dark mode I'm not going to post
on any social media I'm not going to
post on YouTube not going to post post
on Instagram telegram nowhere no more
trade ideas no more free trades
nothing I knew that it was time to
stop and to accept that I had not been
able to cope with the
challenge the time has come to tell my
story and reveal exactly what has
happened so first of all I want to let
you guys know I'm here in Puerto Rico in
a very small island called Gua where I
decided to come here and do my dark mode
uh I've been here for about two weeks
now and it's exactly what I've been
needing because I kind of had to reflect
on the mistakes that I did and this is
pretty crazy because I was pretty much
like a week or 10 days without being on
social media not posting on Instagram
telegram Discord nowhere and that's the
first time I've ever done this in the
last three years because the moment I
decided to take on a community and the
moment I decided to start sharing my
trading and motivating other Traders I
never stopped so it's my first time ever
taking a break but it's very very much
man let me explain to you guys and I've
used this free time that that I haven't
been on social media to think about
swing trading lab my CER forget strategy
the challenge itself my community
everything as a whole this has been
really good for me and for the future of
all of us so first of all I want to
start off by confessing something very
personal about myself and why it led me
to doing what I did in this Challenge
and then after that I'm going to be
answering the most frequently asked
questions that I get on my Instagram
daily about the challenge or
realistically just about my life as a
whole when I entered this dark mode and
what it consist of exactly so now just
let the confession begin so as crazy as
this might sound right now I've always
wanted to be the best Trader in the
world and that's a big big statement to
make but it's real Challenge and I think
I can actually be that guy and I really
truly believe that I can do it trying to
become the best Trader in the world has
brought enormous weight on my back
unnecessary weight because just being a
profitable Trader alone is great but
carrying that title being that figure
that representative of the best Trader
in the world it's not as easy as it
might sound obviously we have the war
and buffets of the world and now we have
the new generation of traders that is
coming in and that are making much
higher percentages than the ogs would
ever make and one of my main ways to
demonstrate how good my skill set is
it's by simply starting this new
challenge what other Trader has done
something like what I did and that
ansers nobody I saw this as the perfect
opportunity to showcase not only my
skill set in front of you guys but for
myself to test myself and this Theory
because if I've always had the mindset
that if you're going to do something
always be the best at it so this is the
perfect challenge for me to take and at
the beginning of it I was actually very
thrilled because I caught some amazing
trades that actually got me out of the
most difficult part of the challenge
which was turning the $100 into $10,000
and it literally filled me With Thrill
because not only was I doing it by
myself but I was doing it in front of
all of you guys and a lot of you guys if
not I'd say 80% of you guys were
catching the same trades as me and
capitalizing off the markets as well so
this filled me with excitement because
everybody's having growth alongside with
me and and I always believed that it was
possible I had my faith intact 100%
solid into the last moment of the
challenge and I'm telling you guys right
now there was nobody out there that
believed that I was going to be able to
complete this challenge more than myself
I was so confident that I was going to
achieve it and in fact this mindset of
me becoming the best Trader in the world
is what actually led me to becoming a
profitable Trader because I knew there
was no other option other than winning
and this winning mindset started off
early on when I started making money
month by month and obviously I started
compounding and then just setting new
goals for myself to just get this goal
becoming the best Trader in the world
even me saying it right now in front of
this camera it sounds crazy but I still
think it could be a possibility but this
faith in myself and becoming this best
Trader in the world kind of smacked me
in the face towards the end of the
challenge because I ended up losing 300K
in one single week all of the time and
effort that I put into this challenge
gone like that just because of my
mindset had completely shifted and I had
lost sight of the actual goal I felt
like I fa myself I felt like I failed
the Alex that had promised himself to
become the best Trader I felt like my
mission had just completely crashed and
most importantly to me I feel like I had
failed you guys my community and my
Traders because I see that you guys see
me as an idol in trading and I didn't
complete this challenge in front of you
guys and besides there being actual
technical reasons on why this happened
not you know putting the blame on
anything else there is other reasons but
at the end of the day there's no excuses
I take 100% responsibility for what
happened happened in this challenge my
will to becoming the world's best Trader
will lead me to having systematic
mistakes you know at the end of the day
I am human and I'm very young so I'm
glad I'm taking this challenge early on
so maybe 5 10 years from now I can hold
that title to being the best Trader in
the world and like I said it's actually
very curious because I was able to take
$100 to 10,000 which statistically and
percentage wise is the hardest part and
then taking 300K to the maill I couldn't
achieve that so I'm still wrapping my
head around why because turning 300K to
a mill I was just two flips away from
doing it versus turning 100 to 10,000
it's much harder and after having spent
two weeks here in this Villa you know
just disconnected from social media and
really looking back at my journey
watching all of my YouTube series videos
literally the first week to week 11 and
I'm analyzing what I did wrong and I
realized the mistake I could see what
issue I did that led me to blowing the
account and just completely throwing
everything out the window and that is
the lack of balance in my life so this
challenge at the beginning gave me a
humongous hype it got me really excited
every single morning I was ready to take
a trade every single London session I
was ready to stay up all night I was
just so excited to give it 100% And just
achieve it as fast as I can that's why I
put the 60 days to turn the 100 into the
maill but little did I know what a
waited me ahead was that this challenge
was going to completely ruin my daily
routine it was going to ruin some of my
friendships some of my actual business
operations even my day-to-day regular
life whether it's eating normal sleeping
sleeping normal or even hitting the gym
and during this challenge I had some
really bad habits like you guys can go
and look at some of the clips and you
guys can see how my face was literally
drained my eyes were purple because
there was times where I wouldn't sleep
at all because I would want to watch
every session of the market as I'm
letting hundreds of thousands of dollars
and high percentages of the account just
fluctuating and I'm risking a lot in the
account obviously but I want to make
sure I don't blow it I was sleeping an
average of like two three 4 hours a day
and on the weekends I couldn't catch up
on any rest because my whole entire
sleep schedule was completely messed up
my sleep cycle was completely messed up
because I wanted to be there before
London session I wanted to be there
during London session because I wanted
to enter the scalin and then I wanted to
be there before New York and then catch
New York and then after that you know I
after New York session's over I kind of
have to live you know a normal human
life and that's where all of my energy
was just completely drained I wasn't
eating my balance diet my chef wouldn't
come as normal as he would so I would
just Uber Eats all the time I wasn't
going to the gym so I wasn't clearing my
mind I was just staying home all day and
the the times that I would have to go to
the gym I would just stay home and rest
and take a nap and truthfully like the
type of Trades that I was taking towards
the end of the challenge you guys can
see that they weren't the best I wasn't
analyzing them as I actually would I was
just trying to get over it because I was
really tired and I just wanted to get
the challenge out the way literally all
I was focused on was on a constant
dopamine of like this high that I would
get when I would win a trade on the
challenge and I would post it and the
DMS you guys would send me cuz you guys
would be catching the same trades as
well and I was just chasing this
consistently time and time again because
I'm like you know what I'm almost there
and it's not only me getting to this
goal and not only me achieving this but
it's all of you guys catching it as well
so all I did was just chase that
excitement to me it was probably one of
the best feelings ever because it wasn't
only me winning everybody was winning as
well and then I realized chasing this
dopa mean not only that I leave my
regular routine but my friends my
basketball friends that I would go and
playing basketball everything just went
out the window I was just focused on
just trading obviously I need to had
that Focus to complete the challenge but
my regular life went completely out the
window I was living just for this
Challenge and obviously at the beginning
I was able to control it because I
didn't realize how serious it was to
come ahead but then it got to the point
where it was just trading challenge
catch up on sleep reply to DMS and
that's it nothing else and then all of
this blew up in the last two weeks of
the challenge which were the first two
losing weeks of the challenge everything
just went out the window I entered a
state where I was almost like in denial
I didn't accept the fact that I was
actually blowing the account like I said
I thought I was the best Trader in the
world I pretty much feel like I'm
Invincible I've been profitable for
three years so how can I be blowing this
challenge it just didn't wrap up in my
head so I was doing anything in my power
to not blow the account and then
literally you know one thing led to
another I just started taking trades
that weren't there started scaling into
trades that weren't even in the right
Trend and then it ended up to the point
where I wasn't even taking trades that I
should have taken in the first place it
got to the point where I literally
wanted to start beating the market I
felt like the market owed me something
cuz I'm the best Trader in the world
right so how can the market beat me
impossible and now once that happened I
just was blinded completely all I saw
was red I started taking unnecessary
risk I started scaling into trades that
weren't even there I started adding
positions to trades that weren't even
there I was taking more trades that I
should have ever even taken because once
the faith in myself and the confidence
in myself that I'm the best tra in the
world was gone I just ended up with a
unprofitable Trader mindset and I just
saw read I lost everything I even
realized looking back at this footage
that I wasn't following my set and
forget strategy in the last week with
any of the trades that I had taken
there's a very specific piece in my
strategy that I do not ever take a trade
unless that I have it and all of the
trades that I took in the last week I
did not have that one very specific
piece I had completely lost control of
myself I had lost control of access to
this account that I had grown I had lost
access to the Alex that led me to get to
that point right there and basically
once I had burned the account and I
realized that I wasn't myself at the
beginning of the challenge I said you
know what we have to stop right here I'm
going to pause it we have to realize
what's going wrong because everything
was good the first 9 to 10 weeks where
did everything go wrong and I realized
what it was and I realized that I had to
stop this because I had to analyze what
happened because I have been extremely
well for the last three years in my
trading making consistent profits so
what has led me to now blowing
everything in the last week and what I
realized is that not only the balance in
my life but it's just the way how I was
approaching the challenge I simply
wasn't following my strategy I wasn't
being patient and I thought I was the
king of the world I literally thought
that the market listened to me I thought
that the market had to do whatever I
said and this is something that you know
over the course of three years you
pretty much predict the market every
single day and you know you catch pretty
much every single move you're going to
almost feel like the king of the world
you're going to feel like you can do
anything because you can predict the
market you can basically predict the
future and the one week that I decided
to risk a little bit more on the account
that's the one week the market didn't
want to listen and everything went out
the window so that's why I decided to go
into this dark mode I decided to just
spend time with myself go back to my
daily habits eating my regular food
working out spending time with myself
spending time with my friends with loved
ones and just honestly just living my
life not living for this dopamine effect
of just winning every single time
there's more to life done to that so
after being here for about 2 weeks I
realized that it really wasn't so
serious what happened it's just a
regular losing streak but since I was so
high on my horse since my ego was
through the roof because I had to turn
the 100 to 300K I'm telling you I
literally felt invincible so the fact
that I get beat down it didn't make any
sense to me I literally thought it was
impossible how can I not pass this
challenge how can the market take away
the money that I had just made so I
realized that the problem was my mindset
was myself the way how I was taking
these wins and not being humble about it
I wasn't taking it as a Trader should
take it I was taking it as if it was my
first time winning and as if this is
what the market owed me so after
realizing that it wasn't really that
serious it was just a series of events
that accumulated together that led to
that end result I realized that I just
really have to realign myself to be able
to take on a challenge like this or just
go back into trading as a whole I really
have to humble myself so I'm glad that
the market humbled me because I was
going to humble myself anyways but it
had to get done so that's why I decided
to come to this Villa spend some time
with some really close friends and and
just really disconnect and reconnect
with myself so I can prepare myself for
this new chapter and this new Alex that
I have coming back and the final
conclusion that I came up with is that
I'm going to be realigned with my goals
and that my daily routine and my work
life balance is going to lead me back to
the Alex that I was the Invincible Alex
that would win the markets every single
time the Alex that pretty much achieved
anything the guy that went from Dunkin'
Donuts to having multi-millions of in
cars and being financially free in Just
2 and a half years and this something I
really wanted to share with you guys
because I can you know maybe see some of
you guys enter position like I am and
lose your work life balance just get
lost in this journey and it's not a bad
thing but you need to know how to
balance it you can't just give it your
awe and then just disappear because
you'll end up in a downward spiral how I
was and as crazy as this my sound I
think this could have probably been one
of the best things that could have
happened to me like I needed this higher
low in my life because I'm ready for
this new higher high that I'm about to
create like I just needed this to happen
for this new challenge that I'm going to
do and I'm I'm telling you right now I'm
ready I'm ready that is precisely the
first question that I'm going to be
answering now because it is the most
frequently Asked question that I get
asked on a daily basis on my Instagram
what's next what's going to happen next
on the challenge all I can say is
1111 11-11 of this year I'm going to be
announcing something very very very big
even big bigger than the hundred to the
Moon challenge so from here to then I'm
just going to keep trading with my
community with my Traders keep working
on them on a one-on-one basis and
scaling them and preparing myself for
this next challenge that I'm coming
because it's very very big the second
question is what happened to you that I
ended up blowing the account so it was a
series of things it was a series of my
emotions getting to me I was tired I
wasn't in my house there was news I was
risking more than I should have and I
was not aligning with my strategy so all
of these things as a combination
attacked the account and it pretty much
took it down so it's something that was
going to happen the way I was going you
know I'm actually surprised looking back
at it now on a pretty cold mindset that
it happened at the time that it did I
was surprised that it didn't happen
earlier in the challenge it was just
this balloon that kept getting filled
and filled with air and it just got to
the point where it popped and I'm glad
that I have because now I'm stronger
than ever and I'm ready for the new
challenge the next question is why
didn't I take into account money
management before taking the trade so
this challenge did not have any risk
management in place there's no risk
management when you're flipping an
account but my Max risk that I was doing
was anywhere from 25 to 33% per trade so
I guess that's the risk management that
I took into account when I was trading
it because if not it would have taken me
months of not a year to get to halfway
of where I did in the account so I think
I was risking very high amount but a
realistic amount to get to the point
where I was at and it just had to get
done because if not it would have taken
way too long and it would have required
a lot greater risk to reward to even get
halfway of where I got in this challenge
so I did take into account the risk
management that I was personally okay
with losing which was anywhere from 25
to 33% which I never ever ever do I only
did it with this challenge I regularly
risk anywhere from 1 to 3% on my
personal account the next question is
why did did you trade on NFP so
truthfully told hand on the chest Bible
I did not know it was NFP you guys know
I don't trade news you guys know I don't
even look at Forex Factory I don't look
at any articles I had no idea it was NFP
and I know NFP is the first Friday of
the beginning of every month I didn't
even know it was the first Friday at the
beginning of the month I was so lost
with myself in this challenge all I
cared about was the charts the account
and showing to you guys so you guys can
copy my traits that's all that I cared
about so I have no idea it was NFP and
this is goes back to the reason why I
blew it cuz I had no work life balance I
didn't have any awareness for what was
going on around me so if I would have
known that it was NFP I could guarantee
you that I would have not gone as
aggressive as I did and for that reason
I paid the price and led me to learning
all the mistakes that I had in this
challenge the next question that I get
asked a lot is what leverage am I using
and I used it one to 500 leverage I
guess that's pretty much it I don't know
why you guys asked that so much but I
used a 1 to 500 leverage so you kind of
need to have high leverage to scale an
account kind of impossible to scale an
account on a 1 to 50 leverage not going
to happen the next question is why
didn't you show the broker so I've said
this multiple times I just wanted to
clarify here another time I personally
don't want to recommend anybody to a
broker I don't like recommending people
to a platform that I have no control
over and I can tell you guys right now
full transparency I could be making 150
to I think it was like 175 a month off
of Just signing a deal of promotion with
a broker so the broker that I was doing
The Challenge on if I would have signed
the deal with that one or with a very
similar one or any broker out there they
were willing to sign me a 12-month
contract paying me $150,000 a month just
to promote the broker and I said no
because I wanted to show you guys how I
just only make money from Trading I
don't want to promote anything I don't
want to push you guys into this platform
or have somebody control my social media
so they can force me to promote
something so then they hold me
accountable because now they're paying
me and now they have ownership over me
no I just wanted to show you guys the
trades let's say you want to do a flip
just go choose the broker that you want
I'm not going to recommend you guys to a
broker because then you guys are going
to say I own it I have affiliation I
control it this that I did the no
promotion of broker to show you guys how
legit and how transparent it is because
trust me it'd be really nice to be
collecting 150k am mon from just putting
a link in my bio or putting a Link in
the description and I'm not doing it
just to show you guys how real and how
transparent I am and anybody that does
that out there I don't knock them at all
I salute to them they that's an
opportunity it's a blessing to have a
platform like this and just by putting a
link in the buyo you're getting paid six
figures a month I think that's amazing
but I just didn't feel okay with doing
that so I just decided that I'm just
going to show you guys the trades and
make you guys profitable Traders by just
learning the strategy and you guys pick
the platform on your own so that's the
reason why I didn't show the broker
because I wanted to be transparent I
didn't feel good collecting that money I
didn't want to push you guys to a
platform that I had no control over the
next question is why didn't you share
the my effects book link so it goes back
to the same thing that I just explained
to the broker if I do that I'm pretty
much promoting the broker so I just
explained that so that's the reason why
I didn't the next question is has the
set and forget strategy stopped working
absolutely not I literally made a 100
okay can I just show you the camera
right now you know I'm going to show you
guys let's see if the set and forget
strategy has stopped
working are you getting it yeah 100K
right
now yeah hasn't stopped working I'm
actually taking a screenshot right now
I'm going post it on Instagram um the
strategy has not stopped working what
happened is that the trader stopped
working in this challenge I ended up
just losing myself I wasn't following
the strategy I wasn't following the plan
so the set and foret strategy is
perfectly fine if anything it's better
than ever because I'm improving it and
I'm getting getting it better every
single time that there's a mistake in
myself and I put it out there to the
community my private Discord so you guys
learn from my mistakes and then you guys
can capitalize off of it as well so the
set forget strategy nothing is wrong
with it it's better than ever so the
next question is why did you decided to
get off of social media and
realistically like I told you guys at
the beginning I felt like I had let you
guys down I felt like my mission had
failed uh I felt like the plan had gone
down the drain and I don't know I just
didn't feel good getting on there try
and continue motivating you guys to be a
better Trader and you know teach you
guys when I wasn't happy myself so I
felt like that's fake I can't just
pretend to put up a character to just
motivate you guys when deep down inside
I'm not happy so I got off of social
media like I said to just reconnect with
myself and just feel better and honestly
it's worked better than I ever expected
it's my first time getting off of social
media for 3 years ever since I started
posting I never stopped posting because
I felt like it's my duty to keep
motivating you guys because I I've
always said I've always wanted to be
that person that I wish that I had at
the beginning when I started trading and
realistically now I'm coming back so
much stronger and I'm not a person to
talk a lot so I'll just let my actions
do the talking so next question is what
is the dark mode so what does my dark
mode consist of and that actually
consists of six very key things and this
dark mode I call it the no excuse dark
mode you can be anywhere in the world
you can have access to absolutely
nothing nothing and still do it and if
you don't achieve the requirements of
this dark mode you simply don't want to
get better that's why I call it the no
excuse dark mode so this dark mode
consists of six things so the first one
is get good sleep get your six to seven
hours of sleep so you can have energy
and clear of mind to be able to attack
the day and I'm saying this now because
I was sleeping 2 3 4 hours at night when
I was doing this whole Challenge and
that's kind of would led me to burning
myself out so the first thing is get
good sleep without good sleep you can't
complete everything else that is inside
this dark mode requirement get your 6 to
7 hours of sleep and then you'll be
ready to go so Point number two in the
dark mode is working out now I'm not
telling you go hit the gym go work out
go do cardio go do this stuff no I'm
just saying work out every single day
you have to hit 309 push-ups why 309
because the highest that I got in the
account was 39,000 so in memory of the
highest that we got in the challenge we
have to hit 309 push-ups every single
day now it doesn't have to be 309
push-ups in one session you can hit 100
in the morning 100 in the afternoon and
then 100 before you go to bed if you do
sets of 10 10 10 10 10 10 you'll do the
300 and you won't even realize and the
next day you'll be extremely sore
because you hit the total of the 309
push-ups and this is no excuse you could
be anywhere in the world and you can hit
309 push-ups where you're watching this
video right now you can put the phone
down and you can hit at least 10
push-ups to so just get it started
that's why this is a no excuse dark mode
because let's say if artist say you have
to go to the gym every single day you
can make some excuses because you don't
have access to a gym it's raining the
gym is closed because of another
pandemic or whatever you can hit a
push-up next to your bed before you go
to sleep so there's no excuses onto why
you can't hit these 309 push-ups Point
number three is spending
14.4 minutes a day analyzing your charts
or just trading as a whole now why 14.4
why it's such a random number that is
because every single day there is
1,440 minutes in the day so you're
simply dedicating 1% out of your day to
your craft now some of you guys might
say well that's too little I want to put
more that's not the point the point is
to put 14.4 minutes of 100% laser focus
no phone no YouTube video no music no
distract nothing just 14.4 minutes of
view and the charts alone and and after
you do these 14.4 minutes you get up and
leave there's no reason why you should
be in front of the computer after you've
done your analysis and you've set your
alarms you do that you set and forget
and then you leave that's why it's only
14.4 minutes it is simply 1% of your day
and again this is no excuse because
you're going to trade no matter what
you're watching this video right now and
I can guarantee you've probably spent
more than 14.4 minutes watching it so
you only dedicate 14.4 minutes to the
charts and that is it the fourth point
is going to be eating good now listen to
what I'm saying I'm not saying only eat
salads or only eat vegan or no d none of
that stuff I'm saying eat good if you're
literally driving home and you want to
go through a drive-thru instead of
making a left into a McDonald's or
instead of making uh right into
Chick-fil-A go to a healthier spot just
go to Publix let's say and go get a
chicken sandwich get something that is
good doesn't have to be healthy just
don't get something that's
don't go pay $2 for for a burger when
you can pay let's say $9 for a better
chicken burger something that's grilled
something that's real so it's not about
eating healthy not at all right you have
to eat no matter what I can guarantee
you you probably can't go two days
without eating and if you're going to go
two days without eating don't put the
first thing into your body a piece of
don't make it a McDonald's
McChicken make it something that's good
pay the extra5 $10 whatever the case is
at the end of the day you are what you
eat so if you eat like you're
probably going to feel like so the
fourth point is going to be eat good
that doesn't mean eat healthy or eat
calories or eat this no eat good if
you're going to go eat a pizza eat a
good pizza eat like a boss don't eat
like you're simply just going to get the
hunger out of the way that's not the
point the fifth point and that is
probably one of the most importance and
I personally what I think is going to be
one of the most challenging for you guys
is going to be spending one hour with
yourself no phone no music no
distraction no car nothing 1 hour with
yourself so 1 hour with yourself can
literally be anywhere can be walking can
be just in your living room but no TV
could be in the kitchen could be just
walk in your neighborhood honestly but
not in your bedroom why because you
probably end up lay down and if you end
up laying down you just close your eyes
after 20 minutes and then after 20
minutes boom you're asleep and you can't
spend this hour by yourself right before
you go to sleep because you're going to
end up falling asleep and that's not the
point the point is to you realize and
you're 100% aware
of what is going on in your life if you
spend an hour with yourself let's say at
1:00 in the afternoon you're not going
to go to sleep you're 100% awake you're
100% aware and that's what I need you to
do I need you to be aware of who you are
where you are what you're doing wrong
and how you can get better because you
need to get better and the only way for
you to do that is if you spend time with
yourself and you bring awareness to who
you are and how you do that so spend one
hour with yourself and it has to be with
no distractions no phone no computer no
dog can't do it walking your dog petting
your cat walking your fish doesn't
matter just do it by yourself and it
cannot be done before you go to sleep
because you'll end up falling asleep the
sixth point is going to be no social
media so a complete social media detox
don't go on social media and just scroll
and just waste your time if you guys go
to the settings on your phone and you
guys see how much time you guys spend on
Tik Tok YouTube shorts or Instagram
shorts it is absolutely insane it
happened to me as well I can guarantee
you all the time you waste surfing
through these social media platforms and
you just use it to yourself you're going
to have so much more of an advantage
compared to absolutely anybody else out
there in the world now are you going to
have less information yes but it's Balan
do you want to have a bunch of
information or do you just want to
better yourself what makes you better
you decide now the the no social media
if you for some reason you can't delete
the app off your phone there's many apps
out there for example opal if you
download it it literally locks you from
going into the app it's free you
download it you plug in your credentials
and it literally blocks you from being
able to enter the app this forces you to
not get on the platform so no social
media a complete social media detox and
then last but not least do one good deed
a day this can be as something as simple
as opening the door for the old lady
that's going into the same store as you
it could be as simple as saying good
morning to your mom it could be
something as simple as calling an old
friend or calling somebody that cares
about you and you haven't talked to them
just be like hey I'm good just letting
you know I'm really busy I still love
you I'm still there I'm just focused on
myself right now I can guarantee you
that phone call to that parent to that
sister to that sibling to that family
member can completely change their day
that is one good deed that you can do a
day it can be something extremely simple
and it doesn't cost you anything and
you're going to completely shift that
person's day for the better and that's
good because that brings you back great
energy a simple act calling your uncle
calling your aunt that you haven't
spoken to for months months because you
just simply haven't had the chance
because you're super dialed in into your
journey can completely change your day
and come back to you in a much better
way so that's what my dark mode has been
consisting of uh as you can tell it's a
no excuse dark mode it doesn't cost you
anything it is completely for free and
everything that I've just said every
single person watching this video right
now has access to it there's no excuses
it is a no excuse dark mode I suggest
you try it for 6 days and you guys are
going to see the shift that you're going
to have and it's very simple because if
you're able to dedicate this time to
yourself and if you're able to invest
this routine into yourself you're just
destined for Success so give it a shot
so we're on our last three questions and
one of them is will you quit
trading absolutely not I will be
the best Trader in the world so I am not
quitting trading anytime soon in fact
I'll say this here in front of you guys
right now I'm only getting started this
is the new beginning of me so this is
only just getting started the next
question is what will happen to swing
trading lab with the set and forget
strategy and nothing the weaker two that
I have been completely off of social
media I still get on my weekly calls
with all of my students and I still give
them my top three top four pairs this
trade that I'm in right now that I think
I'm up still 100 I'm up about yeah
100,000 and3 whatever they caught this
trade so I'm not posting on social media
the before and after trades until my
next challenge but I do it with my
students every single week so what's
happening with swing trading lab we're
thriving we're just going to keep
pushing forward and I keep you know the
routine I like having my routine with my
students because keeps me in check and
honestly there's some people in there
that are even better than me like
they're snipers so I'm very excited for
what has to come with swing trading lab
in the center Fus strategy but yeah
we're as good as ever and then what is
my next big goal so it's kind of like
the first points and that is going to be
1111 1111
2023 something big very very big is
going to come but until then enjoy the
ride because I'm getting
ready I can't even say anything I'll
just see you guys on 11-11 so that's
been a little bit of a summary of my
last few months I hope this video makes
you guys happy I hope this video
fulfills you guys because it does for me
I feel like I've gotten a lot off of my
chest and I feel like it's so much
better been able to explain this to you
guys because you know not everything is
what it seems on social media and you
know obviously like I said the balloon
got filled with air and then it popped
and it feels good now that I was able to
find myself again and find my routine
again and come back even stronger than
ever I am extremely grateful and
thankful for all of you guys I read all
of the YouTube comments I read all of
the Instagram DMS and the community
support has led me to making this new
challenge on 11-11 and I really want to
say my appreciation to every single one
of you guys for the love and the support
but like I've said I feel like what
happened to me in this challenge is one
of the best things that could challenge
because it's prepared me for what's
coming next and what's coming next is
bigger than ever I'll see you guys in
the next video